garagegames.com 2004-06-05

# GarageGames - Play Games - Privacy Policy

View our Privacy Policy  
Copyright © 2000 - 2004   
All Rights Reserved 

| 

## Privacy Policy...

GarageGames values the privacy of the people who visit our site. The following is our detailed privacy policy, if you have any questions, feel free to e-mail [info@garagegames.com](mailto:info@garagegames.com) with your questions. 

### GarageGames Privacy Policy

GarageGames Corporation ("GarageGames") provides a variety of online services, from electronic commerce to downloadable files. Because the success of GarageGames is dependent on building and maintaining goodwill with our customers, we are committed to implementing measures designed to protect the privacy of those using our services. Moreover, we see it as our responsibility to set examples and help establish the standards for privacy on the Internet.

Although GarageGames respects the privacy of all those who visit our web site and use our online services, we do collect information from our members and visitors. This Privacy Policy governs your interaction with the GarageGames web site, and your registration for and use of GarageGames' online services. Except as set forth within this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service and other published guidelines, we do not release personally identifiable information about out members and visitors without their permission. 

Please note that GarageGames reviews its privacy practices from time to time, and that those practices are therefore subject to change. We ask that you bookmark and periodically review this page to ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our Privacy Policy. To contact GarageGames about privacy issues, to report a violation of our Privacy Policy, or to raise any other issue, please e-mail us at [webmaster@Garagegames.com](mailto:webmaster@Garagegames.com).

### The information we gather

GarageGames gathers two types of information about users:

  1. Non-personally identifiable information: When visitors come to our web site, we collect and aggregate information indicating, among other things, which pages were visited, the order in which they were visited, and which hyperlinks were "clicked." Collecting such information involves the logging of IP addresses, operating system and browser software used by each visitor to the GarageGames web site. Although such information is not personally identifiable, we can determine from the IP address a visitor's Internet Service Provider and the geographic location of his or her point of connectivity.

The non-personally identifiable information we collect helps us identify the most popular areas of our web site and determine the effectiveness of our promotional activities. In addition, we may disclose some of this information to advertisers to inform them of the number of people who have seen and/or clicked through their advertisements. 

For the same purposes, we may use "cookies" - that is, small text files placed on your computer's hard drive - to help us determine the type of content and sites to which you link, the length of time you spend at any particular area of the GarageGames site, and the GarageGames services you choose to use. Cookies also tell us which advertising you have seen on our site. Essentially, cookies are your identification cards for the GarageGames computers, or servers, that placed them there. Cookies are only read by the server that placed them, and are unable to execute any code or virus. 

Cookies allow GarageGames to serve you better and more efficiently, and to personalize your experience at GarageGames' web site. Nevertheless, you should be able to control how and whether cookies will be accepted by your web browser. For more information on how to do so, please refer to the documentation accompanying your browser. 

  2. Personally identifiable information: In certain areas of the GarageGames web site - for example, when registering to become an GarageGames member - we request, but do not require, that you provide us with personally identifiable information (including, for example, first name, surname, street address, email address, telephone number, and when applicable, credit card information). 

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children (defined herein as minors younger than thirteen years of age) without obtaining parental consent. Before registering for membership with GarageGames, we ask that children have their parents read our Privacy Policy. Before and during the registration process, we encourage children to include a parent or guardian in the process. 

GarageGames does not control the acts of its members or visitors. All members and visitors should be aware that, when they disclose personally identifiable information in a bulletin board, chat room, guestbook, or other forum, the information may be collected and used by others to send that person unsolicited email from other parties outside GarageGames. In the event that you encounter any GarageGames user who is improperly collecting or using information about you or other users, please contact [webmaster@Garagegames.com](mailto:webmaster@Garagegames.com).

### How we use (and do not use) the information we gather

Please take some time to familiarize yourself with the different ways GarageGames uses the information that it gathers. Keep in mind that, while GarageGames encourages all third parties involved - including but not limited to its affiliates and advertisers - to adhere to our policies regarding the privacy of our visitors and members and to otherwise handle personal information in a responsible manner, we cannot and do not assume any responsibility for any actions or omissions of third parties, including the manner in which they use information received either from GarageGames or independently. Nevertheless, in the event you encounter any third party associated with, or who claims association with GarageGames who you feel is improperly collecting or using information about you, please contact [webmaster@Garagegames.com](mailto:webmaster@Garagegames.com); we will be happy to forward your message to the third party.

  1. How we use (and do not use) non-personally identifiable information: We use non-personally identifiable information in aggregate form to build higher quality, more useful online services by performing statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of our members and visitors, and by measuring demographics and interests regarding specific areas of the GarageGames web site. We provide statistical information based on this data to advertisers, affiliates, and other current and potential business partners. We also use the aggregate data to inform these third parties as to the number of people who have seen and clicked on links to their web sites. 

The GarageGames web site contains links to other Internet web sites, including co-branded or other affiliated sites which may or may not be owned or operated by GarageGames. Unless otherwise explicitly stated, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites, including such sites' use of any information (such as IP number, browser type, or operating system) collected when visitors to the GarageGames web site click through links to those sites. Even though such information might not identify you personally, we strongly encourage you to become familiar with the privacy practices of those sites.

  2. How we use (and do not use) personally identifiable information: GarageGames provides notice to potential GarageGames registrants that personally identifiable information will be collected during the registration process. Such notice is provided simultaneously with your GarageGames registration; moreover, this Privacy Policy itself serves as notice that such information is collected under those circumstances. Although you may not "opt out" of the registration process if you wish to become a GarageGames member, you may choose to "opt out" of receiving promotional materials from GarageGames and/or its affiliates, advertisers, or other business partners. If you do not "opt out" of receiving such promotional materials, GarageGames reserves the right to release any personally identifiable registration information regarding you to third parties who provide goods or services that we believe may be of interest to you. We will not release your credit card information to third parties unless necessary to complete a transaction between you and such a third party. If you decide that you would like to discontinue receiving promotional information from such third parties, please contact those third parties directly, or contact GarageGames at [info@Garagegames.com](mailto:info@Garagegames.com).

GarageGames limits its own e-mail solicitations to those customers who have not "opted out" of receiving such communications. The solicitations are limited in that they, among other things, will clearly indicate the originator of the e-mail and provide the customer with a method of "opting out" of receiving future communications of a similar nature. 

In addition, GarageGames sometimes uses individual data to "target" advertising - to decide which advertisements and sponsor messages to show to which members. As an example, if Sponsor Co. wishes to display their advertising only to female GarageGames members, GarageGames uses member registration data to ensure that Sponsor Co.'s ads are displayed only to female members. 

Finally, GarageGames may use individual members' data to "pre-populate" forms which are displayed for the purpose of collecting individual data by GarageGames and/or its sponsors. In no case does pre-populating a form automatically transfer any data to any advertiser or third party. Only if the member voluntarily requests that such data be transferred will any transfer take place - for example, if/when a member clicks a "submit form" button or other button. 

We reserve the right to release information contained within our access logs concerning any visitor or member when that visitor or member is in violation of our Terms of Service or other published guidelines, or partakes (or is reasonably suspected of partaking) in any illegal activity, even without a subpoena, warrant, or other court order, and to release such information in response to discovery requests. We cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who may be using our servers or services for illegal activities. We also reserve the right to report any suspected illegal activity to law enforcement for investigation or prosecution.

If and when GarageGames sponsors promotions or sweepstakes, or third parties sponsor promotions or sweepstakes in conjunction with GarageGames, either GarageGames or the third party will post relevant privacy information in the official rules and/or registration area for the promotion or sweepstakes. That privacy information, to the extent it conflicts with this Privacy Policy, will govern that particular promotion or sweepstakes. 

### Changing or deleting personal information

If you would like to have your personally identifiable information removed from GarageGames' database, please contact us at [webmaster@Garagegames.com](mailto:webmaster@Garagegames.com), and we will use reasonable efforts to comply with your request. Keep in mind, however, that there will be residual information that will remain within GarageGames databases, access logs, and other records, which may or may not contain such personally identifiable information. The residual information will not be used for commercial purposes; however GarageGames reserves the right, from time to time, to recontact former customers or users of GarageGames.

### Questions?

Questions regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to GarageGames at [webmaster@Garagegames.com](mailto:webmaster@Garagegames.com).

|
